"Ready or not, here I come"
"If you want to play hide and seek,
gather up here"
[So dark that even the moonlight is dim]
Hey! Is anyone there?
Oh my god
TARZZAN? YOUNGSEO?
-ANNIE?
[The five members go their separate ways in the unfamiliar place]
-TARZZAN, where you at?
TARZZAN?
Where is everyone?
I'm terrified
I'm scared...
What is this?
Sigh...
Wait, I'm so scared
I'm terrified
Oh my god
I'm so scared right now
What do I do?
-We shouldn't stay together
-It's over if we stay together
[It's over if we stay together]
-The game is over for us
-The game is over
They're here
Who are you?
[Someone is chasing after me]
There we go
Okay
Oh my god
The foreigner always dies first
Are you all done hiding?
I'm coming to find you now.
I just heard the cane.
I heard the cane.
Hold on
Sigh...
How do I turn off this light?
Do I just unplug it?
There we go
[Stay hidden and survive]
Wow
Where am I?
Can I move?
[TARZZAN on B1]
Oh my god
Where am I?
You can't see in here
[Special effects turn on]
What is this?
Someone keeps washing their hands...
This is a tire
Why am I the only one in the hallway?
Why isn't anyone
coming out to the hallway?
Am I the only one here?
[YOUNGSEO on 1F]
-Woah, that surprised me
[Another person on the first floor]
[YOUNGSEO and WOOCHAN on 1F]
Woah
I'm scared
What's this?
A phone! The ringing
I need to lower the volume
There we go,
I know you're supposed to do that
I've seen a lot of these clips
Woah!
[Special effects turn on]
Woah
I'm scared
[WOOCHAN's breathing]
I thought that was a person!
[WOOCHAN heads up to the second floor]
Somebody else?
I'm scared
No, there's definitely someone up here
[Heads to the third floor to find another member]
[ANNIE on 3F]
[ANNIE woke up on the third floor]
Hold up, what's this?
I'm terrified
[Special effects turn on]
Oh my god
[Phone notification sound]
Did I get notification on my phone?
I got a text
[Right when she's checking her phone]
[Footsteps come near her]
Something's here
[WOOCHAN appeared in front of ANNIE]
[WOOCHAN wandering the hallways on the third floor]
Is anyone there?
[Heads in the room with a flashlight]
I'm scared
We have to hide
We have to hurry and hide
I'm scared!
[The two move together]
I'm scared
Hurry up!
Hey!
[Heads out to the balcony]
No, I have to
check the text message
It tells you to find a key
I think you can hide here
No, I need to check the text...
[The door shuts]
I almost swore
Hey!
We need to find a key
Get down
I'm going to go find the key
Don't follow me
Wait
Don't follow me!
ANNIE!
I told you not to follow me
Don't follow me!
It's here
Get down
[While these two are busy hiding]
[BAILEY is still alone on the fourth floor]
[Sound of BAILEY's sigh]
[Standing next to the stairs]
[TARZZAN]
I get no service over here
[There's no service down in the basement]
Woah
[Can hear something far away]
I just heard the sound of a cane
I heard the sound of the cane
[Escapes to the first floor]
[Special effects turn on]
But I need to go find the others
[Phone notification sound]
[Gets a text the moment he comes up to the first floor]
Safety...
[Someone stepped on the trap]
[Follows the sound of the trap]
[Sound of someone talking]
[Found YOUNGSEO at the end of the hallway]
Can I go in the fridge?
Oh, it's you
Why did you sneak over so quietly?
I didn't hear anyone else
so I assumed
nobody else came to the hallway
I was totally sneaking around
Really? Was I the only one
talking to myself like this?
You followed the sound of my voice, right?
But they're telling us to find a key
We have to find a key?
-Oh, I had a phone
-In the text
I just saw this
I had a phone, that's right
Yeah, let's look for the key
[Start looking for the hidden key]
[Once you get caught, you can free yourself with a key]
[or use it to save other members (one key per escape)]
Let's look for the key
Oh~
Oh, what's this?
[Trap]
[TARZZAN takes the trap]
They must've put that there
so it makes a sound
if you step on it
-That surprised me
-You totally have a delicate heart
I was super scared
I came from the basement
Really? Did you walk over here?
Yeah, I memorized the map a bit now
Oh, then can you give me
a tour of the place?
Okay
I haven't been over here
Let's check this place out
[TARZZAN and YOUNGSEO on 1F]
Be careful
I wasn't able to get out of here
[ANNIE and WOOCHAN still on the third floor balcony]
Don't leave!
You have to go that way
We have to split up
We can't stick together
When are they going to
start chasing after us?
I don't know, but if we stick together,
there's a higher chance we'll get caught
Get lost!
You want me to get lost?
Hurry up and get lost!
This is my spot
[WOOCHAN heads in the room]
[Waiting in front of the door]
Boo!
Are you out of your mind?
[The two head up to the fourth floor]
[WOOCHAN gets startled]
That scared me
[Found BAILEY on the fourth floor]
What are you doing?
You scared me
Like right now...
What are you doing?
What are you doing? Hold on
No, we can't be doing this
We have to look for the key
We have to find a key
No, we can't be sticking together
Oh! This!
You need to check the texts on your phone
Oh, I didn't know
I could've just headed down
Find the key
I'll look for the key here
Why is this place so big?
I better look for the key
Not here
[The three look around the third floor]
[ANNIE, WOOCHAN and BAILEY on 3F]
[TARZZAN and YOUNGSEO on 2F]
[TARZZAN and YOUNGSEO head up to the second floor]
We'll set this up
right in front of the door like this
[The trap from the first floor]
Like this
-If you hear it (someone is there)
-You brought it for the squeak?
So if we have this
and we put it right in front of
the room we're hiding in
we'll hear a squeak
if the seeker comes here
I don't think
they even installed cameras here
[TARZZAN looks around after setting up the trap]
But...
I don't think
they even set up cameras out here
so the only cameras
are the ones we have
-Hey
-This...
Hey you
Don't you think you'll be safe
if you stand over there?
-Where?
-That block down there
[Here]
Have you lost it?
I want to find the others first
If we're all grouped up...
[Collects the trap and heads back in the room]
[Something caught on YOUNGSEO's foot]
-Hey, is this a trap?
Hold up
I feel like
this is the first spot they'll check
Let's get things that can make a sound...
[Phone notification sound]
I got something on my phone
Let's set things up over here
that can make sounds
[While TARZZAN is setting up traps for the seeker]
[YOUNGSEO checks the text]
TARZZAN!
TARZZAN
[Key hint]
They sent a photo
What's this?
What's this? Right?
[Photo sent to those on the third floor as well]
[Key hint]
Fire extinguisher!
No, I have to go down a floor
I have to go down here
[ANNIE on the move after checking the hint]
[Key hint]
It's over there?
Okay
Go down!
[WOOCHAN heads down as well]
(Stops)
The seeker...
Hey!
[WOOCHAN starts by hiding at the sound of someone]
[ANNIE arrived on the second floor,
just barely missing WOOCHAN]
Hey!
It's me!
Who are you?
[Trap]
[YOUNGSEO startled at TARZZAN's trap]
[TARZZAN laughs]
[ANNIE goes in the room WOOCHAN is hiding in]
-I don't know how to check the text
-Hey!
ANNIE ran away without us
How are we
supposed to find the key?
I think ANNIE is in here
You scared me
Boo!
-You scared me
-There was actually someone in the coffin
No, we can't stick together
I don't care,
it's lonely being alone
Who have you met so far?
I met everyone, including BAILEY
Where's BAILEY?
Upstairs
We have to go upstairs
Okay, I'm playing this solo
Guys, I'm going to do this solo
I'm going to wait
until the others leave...
-Did you check the photo they sent?
-What's this?
I set this up
Did you see the photo
of the fire extinguisher?
Yeah I did
I'm going to check upstairs
[WOOCHAN steps on TARZZAN's trap]
That scared me
[Scared at the camera this time]
What a scaredy-cat
[TARZZAN's laugh]
Sigh
He stepped on the thing I set up earlier
I know
BAILEY!
BAILEY?
[TARZZAN and YOUNGSEO on 3F]
-I've met everyone except BAILEY so far
Wow...
[Meanwhile, BAILEY]
[Is already on the second floor]
(Hesitant)
[TARZZAN and YOUNGSEO looking for BAILEY]
[BAILEY]
BAILEY!
BAILEY?
[The three just missed each other]
-BAILEY!
[ANNIE heads out the room and finds BAILEY]
Oh my god
I saw clues
A clue?
I saw something
What is that?
Okay, calm down.
I saw a clue
[ANNIE and BAILEY heads to the third floor]
[ANNIE, BAILEY,TARZZAN and YOUNGSEO on 3F]
-I don't know where the stairs
next to the fire extinguisher is
This place is big
Yeah, this place is big
Come up here
But there's a ton of rooms...
Yeah, the seeker will never find us
There's a trap here too
[TARZZAN grabs the trap and heads out the room]
-There are a lot of traps
Come up here
[Found ANNIE and BAILEY]
Stop!
Those two are together
[Phone notification]
I got a text
[Key hint, second floor]
-Where is that?
That's where the key is
There's like a first aid kit
We just roamed around chatting
I'm not getting messages
This one
[While the three of them discuss]
No, go to your messages
[ANNIE heads down to find the key first]
[WOOCHAN on the second floor]
So when's the seeker coming after us?
That scared me
[Startled at ANNIE and BAILEY]
-That scared me
Hey!
Hey BAILEY!
Hey ANNIE!
[Nobody is on the second floor]
I think the seeker is coming
[Goes into a room to escape the seeker]
[Key hint, second floor]
The key is definitely here
There's definitely a key here...
It's a key, I found it
I found it
[WOOCHAN gets the first key]
[Trap]
Because I found a key,
it's fine to get caught
[Just then]
TARZZAN!
[Members gather on the second floor]
I found a key!
-Where?
-There's another one on the first floor
The first aid kit?
I found the one in the first aid kit
What's on the first floor?
-It's near the fire extinguisher
-The fire extinguisher
But we can't all go
because the seeker
will come from the first floor
Fire extinguisher on the first floor!
I'll go there
I better go there
[TARZZAN heads down to the first floor]
-Fire extinguisher...
Fire extinguisher...
[Trap]
[Heads back up to the second floor]
Hey
There are way too many seekers
down on the first floor
Are there seekers down there?
Yeah, I heard them
stepping on the trap
[Checks the first floor right away but can't see anything]
[TARZZAN]
[TARZZAN heads back down to the first floor]
You said there were a lot of
seekers down there
so why is he going down there?
[TARZZAN starts crawling]
[Mistook the fire cabinet as the fire extinguisher]
[Meanwhile, ANNIE]
[Key hint, first floor]
The fire extinguisher
on the first floor, okay
Fire extinguisher on the first floor...
I'm going to head down to the first floor
to find the fire extinguisher
[Special effect turning on]
[ANNIE on 1F]
[Finally found the key]
I found it
[ANNIE gets the second key]
[Phone notification]
[Key hint, third floor]
-It's at the fire cabinet
-Huh?
[WOOCHAN opening up places that look similar]
Oh!
[Did they find a key?]
Is it in here?
[Didn't find a key but found somewhere to hide]
No, you can't go there
I can't? Why not?
Have you opened this one up?
No
Is there anything there?
[Fire cabinet from the hint]
[The door on the top doesn't open]
[Tries to open the door on the bottom]
[Found a key]
Woah!
[The moment they pull the key]
[WOOCHAN's scream]
[BAILEY's scream]
You found it?
[TARZZAN's scream]
Now I'm the seeker
I found two keys
We have two lives
I found one key
You found a key?
Hey, they're coming now
[All the members are on the third floor]
-We can't group up like this
-The game is over if we're grouped up
-It's game over
-Then you follow me
-Hurry up
[TARZZAN moves with BAILEY]
I didn't hide yet, you punk
Oh my god
[TARZZAN and BAILEY went
downstairs to the basement]
This place is terrifying
You don't get service down here
So here?
What are we looking for now?
We're not looking for something,
we're hiding
-We have to hide
-Okay
"Ready or not"
"here I come"
Here
Here's the best spot
"Ready or not TARZZAN, here I come"
[TARZZAN and BAILEY on B1]
[ANNIE looking for a place to hide on the third floor]
-"Ready or not"
[Phone notification sound]
"Here I come, ANNIE"
[Goes behind the open door]
[Phone notification sound]
-Hurry over here
Hide and seek begins now
[Playtime is 4,444 seconds]
-Playtime is four hours?
[If you get caught by the seeker, you'll be sent to jail]
-It's 4,444 seconds
[If 50% or more people survive]
-DAY ONE might receive a huge gift
[DAY ONE may receive a huge gift,
so do your best to stay alive]
Are you done hiding?
I'm coming to get you now
[Hide and seek begins]
[ANNIE, WOOCHAN and YOUNGSEO on 3F]
-How do I turn this on and off?
-It's on the back
-Where?
You have to tell me how to use this
Oh, okay
Wow, but the beginning
was really terrifying
For real
The seeker is basically a zombie right now
No, they looked like a Korean ghost
They gave off the succubus vibe
[Seeker, ANNIE, WOOCHAN and YOUNGSEO on 3F]
[Seeker is on the third floor]
[ANNIE]
-I think this is a pretty safe spot
I better stay here
I'm terrified, what do I do?
[ANNIE]
[Seeker]
[Makes a turn and heads downstairs]
Did the seeker go somewhere else?
[TARZZAN and BAILEY on B1]
It's so hot
[TARZZAN and BAILEY
-laid down under the basement machine]
[Sound of the seeker]
Shh
[Seeker arrived at the basement]
[TARZZAN, BAILEY and Seeker on B1]
[Seeker]
[TARZZAN and BAILEY]
[The seeker and the duo
are getting closer to each other]
[TARZZAN and BAILEY]
[Passes the members and
heads deep into the basement]
[TARZZAN heads out the moment
the seeker disappears]
[TARZZAN]
[Quickly calls for BAILEY]
[The seeker comes back]
[Seeker]
[BAILEY]
[The seeker passes by BAILEY]
[TARZZAN]